<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.4.0">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2025-01-29T16:43:31-05:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Geek Grimoire</title><subtitle>A place for all of the PFM I have learned over the years, and am still learning
</subtitle><author><name>Jefferson Kirkland</name><email>numberwhun@gmail.com</email></author><entry><title type="html">Welcome, To The Geek Grimoire!</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/intro/2025/01/29/Welcome-To-The-Geek-Grimoire.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Welcome, To The Geek Grimoire!" /><published>2025-01-29T00:00:00-05:00</published><updated>2025-01-29T00:00:00-05:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/intro/2025/01/29/Welcome-To-The-Geek-Grimoire</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/intro/2025/01/29/Welcome-To-The-Geek-Grimoire.html"><![CDATA[<p>Welcome, to the Geek Grimoire!</p>

<p>I have been out of the blogging sphere for quite a while.  I’ve mostly been learning, reading and working.  Covid, while causing a whole lot of disruptions, also forced companies to allow working from home.  While there are a number of companies requiring workers to return, some, like where I work with a global team, have found that we work just as well, if not better, at home than in the office.  The WFH part also allows many of us to handle at-home things, that wouldn’t have been possible to do while away in the office.  For me, at least, its been a very positive experience.</p>

<p>The last blog I had was on Blogger.  For a while, I was blogging things I learned.  Almost as a cheatsheet for myself, but also so I wouldn’t forget what I had learned.  It was pretty much my brain book, as it were.  I got tired of the Blogger platform as a whole, and wanted something I had more control over.  Plus, I needed to get out from under paying anually for a domain name.  Enter, Github Pages.</p>

<p>With a small learning curve, here I am.  Starting a new place to dump all of my technical learnings and knowledge.  I have been exposed to a plethora of new tech at the current job, and look forward to sharing it here.  I will also be importing some things that I posted on my other site.  (While the Blogger site is still up, I am no longer blogging there)</p>

<p>You won’t find any politics, religion or whatnot here.  This is going to be solely for my geek stuff.  I hope you like some of the things I post and find them useful in your work or hobby activities.</p>

<p>Without further ado, let’s get to filling this Grimoire with information.</p>

<p>Happy Geeking!</p>]]></content><author><name>[&quot;Jefferson Kirkland&quot;]</name></author><category term="intro" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome, to the Geek Grimoire!]]></summary></entry></feed>